

SOFIA BLOMGREN

070-692 87 11 sofiablo@kth.se www.sofiablomgren.me

ABOUT ME

I'm 28 years old and I grew up in Stockholm, Sweden. After high school I moved to Santa Barbara, California, where I studied photography and media for two years at college. Right now I'm on the last year of the masters program in Media Technology at KTH in Stockholm. I'm also freelancing as a photographer through my own business. I'm a positive person who likes to plan and coordinate things, something that I've practiced a lot through many of the experiences mentioned below. After graduating I want to work with user experiece and, eventually, project management.

EDUCATION

M.Sc.Eng. Media Technology, M.Sc. Interactive Media Technology		2015-present
	KTH Royal Institute of Technology Stockholm, Sweden	
B.Sc. Media Technology		2015-2018
	KTH Royal Institute of Technology Stockholm, Sweden	

2012-2014

2015-present

2018

2017-2018

Certificate of Achievement in Applied Photography

Santa Barbara City College Santa Barbara, CA, USA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fast Travel Games	Spring 2020
Master Thesis Student Researching UX for hand tracking in VR.	
Ericsson	Summer 2019

Summer Intern

Summer intern working with UI and UX design for a VR project.

Sofia Blomgren Photography

Owner, Photographer & Videographer

My own business through which I take different freelance photo and video jobs.

Rockfoto

Photo EditorRockfoto is a photo agency for concert photography. As photo editor, I work as a coordinator between clients, concert promoters and our photographers.

PhotographerRockfoto is a photo agency for concert photography. As photographer, I take photos at concerts and then deliver the photos to a tight deadline.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Chapter of Media Technology, KTH

Head of the Photo Committee	2018-2019
The Photo Committee is a group for everyone at the chapter	
who's interested in photography. As head of the committee, I	
created events for its members and worked together with other	
committees at the chapter when they needed photographers.	

Project Leader of the Student Reception

I was one of three project leaders of the student reception at the chapter. Being project leader includes recruiting students to work during the reception, planning the whole reception and being main responsible during all reception events.

Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As

photographer, I took photos for articles that I was assigned and

Osqledaren, KTH

delivered to a deadline.

Media Producer Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As media producer, I create content for web and social media.	2018-present
Photo Editor Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As photo editor, I was responsible for the photographers and illustrators on the editorial staff and I guided them through the creative process. I was also a part of the paper's project group.	2016-2017
Photographer	2015-2016,